{
    "id": "b28f9f3df9aa45bb9122b0a4b0190ad1",
    "title": "General Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The retiring chairman received a …………………… from the new chairman.",
            "description": "All of these words can mean praise.",
            "answers": [
                "panegyric",
                "tribute",
                "eulogy",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Because the old couple was …………………………… they never had to ask for financial help.",
            "description": "Parsimonious means frugal.",
            "answers": [
                "spendthrift",
                "parsimonious",
                "openhanded"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The car …………………………. the truck at 70 miles an hour.",
            "description": "Passed is the past tense of pass.",
            "answers": [
                "passed",
                "past"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Did you see a car go …………………………….?",
            "description": "Go past means go across one’s field of vision.",
            "answers": [
                "passed",
                "past",
                "pass"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Stamp collecting is an agreeable …………………………",
            "description": "Pastime is the correct spelling.",
            "answers": [
                "pastime",
                "passtime",
                "pasttime"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The difference in their heights is hardly ……………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "perceptible",
                "perceivable",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Should parents be strict or ……………………….?",
            "description": "Permissible means permitted. Permissive means lenient.",
            "answers": [
                "permissible",
                "permissive"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Is this a business call or a …………………………….. one?",
            "description": "Personal means belonging to a particular person.",
            "answers": [
                "personal",
                "personnel"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "All ……………………… will receive an extra week’s vacation.",
            "description": "Personnel means employees or workers.",
            "answers": [
                "personnel",
                "personal"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The …………………………….. were observed by astronomers throughout the world.",
            "description": "Phenomena is plural phenomenon is singular.",
            "answers": [
                "phenomenon",
                "phenomena"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The disease was discovered in an early ……………………………..",
            "description": "Phase means stage.",
            "answers": [
                "phase",
                "pace",
                "face"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Cook the beans with a ……………………………….. of salt pork.",
            "description": "Piece means a portion or share.",
            "answers": [
                "peace",
                "piece",
                "peas"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}